Ross,she wants you.
告訴你吧,羅斯,她要你
We just live in the same building.
我們只是住在同一棟公寓
-Any contact? -She lent me an egg.
-有過任何接觸? -她借過我一顆蛋
-You're in! -Right.
-有機會了 -真的
Hey,Ross.
嗨,羅斯
Come on. Get back in the game.
拜託,你得再接再厲
The Rachel thing isn't happening, your ex-wife's a lesbian....
你和瑞秋的事沒指望 你前妻是個女同志
I don't think we need a third.
我們不想有第三回
Could we get an egg, still in the shell?
抱歉,能給我們個蛋嗎?整顆蛋?
An egg?
蛋?
Go up to her and say, "I'm returning your egg."
對,你拿這顆蛋去還她
I think it's winning.
我們贏定了
-It's insane. -She'll love it.
-拜託,這太離譜了 -她會喜歡的
-Thank you. -Thank you. Here.
-謝謝 -謝謝,給
Go with the egg,my friend.
朋友,帶著蛋去
Go,go,go!
快去
-Think it'll work? -No way. It's suicide.
-你想會成功嗎? -才怪,這簡直是自殺.帶蛋的男人
The One With The Candy Hearts
六人行 第1季 第14集 情人節糖果
-=BT之家DRM小組 http://bbs.btbbt.com=- 榮譽出品 河馬根據網絡字幕微調製作
-You can't do this. -Do what?
-你不能這樣做 -做什麼?
-Roger wants to take her out. -No! Remember why you dumped him?
-羅傑明天要帶她出去 -不,菲比難道你忘了為何拋棄他?
Because he was creepy.
因為他惹人厭
And mean. And frightening.
卑鄙又可怖
Still,it's nice to have a date on Valentine's Day!
但情人節有人共渡也不差
You can go out with a creep any night.
其他任何一夜跟他約會都無所謂
I know I do.
我知道我會這麼做
-What are you doing tomorrow night? -That depends on how tonight goes.
-你們明晚有何節目? -明天有何節目全看今天的表現
-About tonight -Don't you bail on me!
-關於今晚 -你不能背叛我
I said I'd bring a friend for her friend.
我答應為她朋友帶一位男伴
-But her friend sounds like a -Pathetic mess. I know,but....
-我知道,但她朋友好像是個… -可憐蟲,我知道
Come on. She's needy,vulnerable.
但她是如此渴望如此脆弱
I'm thinking....
我想.
Thanks.
謝謝
You haven't been out with a woman since Janice. You're doing this.
你和珍妮絲之後就沒約過會 你一定要去
-She said yes. -Way to go,man!
-她答應了 -幹得好
Still got the egg,huh?
-蛋還在?. -對
How do I look?
我的樣子如何?
I don't care.
不關我的事
There's Lorraine.
蘿拉妮來了
No trading. You get the pretty one, I get the mess.
切記,不准交換 你有美女相伴,我有賤貨作陪
Hi,Joey.
喬依
Well,well! Look what you brought!
瞧你帶什麼人來
Very nice.
真帥
And what did you bring?
你帶誰來?
She's checking her coat.
她在放外套
I'm gonna wash the cab smell off of my hands.
我去洗掉手上的出租車味
Get me a white zinfandel, and a glass of red for Janice.
你幫我和珍妮絲點萄葡酒和紅酒
Janice?
珍妮絲…
Janice!?
Oh...
哦…
... my...
… 我的…
...God!
…天哪!
Hey,it's Janice!
是珍妮絲
Okay,I'm making a break for it!
我得逃了,我要從窗子爬出去
I've been waiting for,like,forever to go out with Lorraine.
我一直夢想與蘿拉妮約會
-Just calm down. -Calm down?
-冷靜點.. -冷靜?
You set me up with a woman I've dumped twice in the last five months!
你竟撮合我與在五個月內 被我甩掉兩次的女人
Can you stop yelling? You're making me nervous and....
別這麼大聲行嗎?你害我緊張得…
I can't go when I'm nervous.
我一緊張就尿不出來
I'm sorry,you're right.
抱歉,你說得對
Come on! Do it,do it!
拜託!快點
Roger was creepy,but he was nothing compared to Pete.
羅傑雖討人厭 但與彼得卡尼相較還差得遠呢
-Who? -Pete the Weeper.
-誰? -愛哭鬼彼德
The guy that used to cry every time we had sex?
我們每次做愛他就哭
"Was it good for you?"
你滿足嗎?
I'd take crying any day over Howard,the "I win" guy!
我每天都想為霍爾那個傢伙哭
"I win! I win!"
「我贏!我贏!」
We went out for two months. I didn't win once.
我和他約會兩個月一次都沒贏過
How do we end up with these jerks?
我們怎會和這些渾蛋在一起?
We're some kind of magnets.
我們可是良家婦女
I know I am. That's why I can't wear a digital watch.
我知道我有 所以我不能戴電子錶
There's more beer,right?
還有啤酒?
You know my friend who shaves her head?
記得我那剃光頭的朋友艾比?
No.
No. 不
I have this friend who shaves her head.
我那剃光頭的朋友
She says to break the bad boyfriend cycle...
她說想要停止與惡男交往的惡性循環
...you can do a cleansing ritual.
可以舉行一個清理儀式
Pheebs,this woman is voluntarily bald.
菲比,她是個大禿頭
Yeah.
是的
We can do it tomorrow night.
我們明晚可以試試看
It's Valentine's Day. It's perfect.
明天情人節是絕佳的時刻
Okay,what kind of ritual?
什麼儀式?
We can burn the stuff they gave us.
我們可以燒掉他們送的東西
Or...?
或者是?
Or we can chant and dance around naked with sticks.
或是唸經,拿著權杖裸體跳舞
Burning's good.
還是燒東西好
You know...
知道嗎
... I can pick up quarters with my toes.
我從兒時就能用腳趾夾起25美分
Yeah? Good for you.
是嗎?真厲害
Quarters or rolls of quarters?
硬幣還是紙幣?
By the way,I cut you out of all of my pictures.
對了,錢德我把照片上的你都剪掉了
So if you want,I have a bag with just your heads.
如果需要,我有一袋你的頭
That's okay.
不用了
You could make little puppets out of them.
你可以用它們做傀儡
And you could use them in your Theater of Cruelty!
也可以在你的「殘酷戲院」中用它們!
-We can't do that! -What? What can't you do?
-不能這麼做 -什麼?不能做什麼?
Can I talk to you for a second? Over there?
能過去和你談談嗎?
We might be leaving now.
我們得先離開
Tell me it's you and me "we."
告訴我「我們」是指你和我
She wants to slather my body with stuff and lick it off.
她說她要在我身上塗滿東西 然後舔乾淨
I'm not even sure what slathering is!
我甚至不知道塗是什麼意思
But I definitely want to be a part of it!
但我絕對不想錯過任何部分!
Okay,you cannot do this to me.
你不能這樣待我
You're right. I'm sorry.
你說得對,抱歉
Can we have three chocolate mousses to go?
三份巧克力慕斯外帶
I'm out of here.
我走了
Here's my credit card. Dinner's on me.
這是我的信用卡,這一頓算我的
I hope she throws up on you.
我希望把她扔在你身上
Thanks.
謝謝
-So.... -Just us.
只剩下我們
What a crappy night!
真是糟糕的一夜
I have enjoyed the fact...
但我還是一直欣賞
...that your shirt's been sticking out of your zipper.
你拉鏈裡的衣服
Excuse me.
抱歉
How you doing?
近來可好?
So do we have the best friends, or what?
他們是我們最要好的朋友?
Joey's not a friend. He's...
喬伊哪兒稱得上是朋友,他…
...a stupid man who left us his credit card.
他這留下信用卡的笨蛋
Another drink? Dessert? A big-screen TV?
想再來一杯?甜點?大銀幕電視?
-I'll have a drink. -Got it. Good woman!
-我想再來一杯 -沒問題,好女人
-A bottle of overpriced champagne. -Each.
-拿瓶最貴的香檳來 -每人一瓶
That's right,each. And a rob roy.
對,再每人各一瓶羅伯羅伊
I've always wanted to know.
我老早就想品嚐了
Happy Valentine's Day!
情人節快樂
Oh,I miss you already.
我現在就開始想念你了
-Can you believe this happened? -No,no!
-你能相信會發生這種事嗎? -不能
And yet it did.
但還是發生了
-Goodbye,Janice. -kiss me!
-再見,珍妮絲 -吻我
Oh,Chandler. Sorry.
錢德,抱歉
Oh,Chandler. Sorry!
-Hey,Janice. -Hi,Monica.
-珍妮絲 -摩尼卡
Well,this was very special.
真是太特別了
Rach,come see who's out here!
瑞秋,看誰來了
What's going on? Oh,my God!
怎麼了?天啊
Janice! Hi!
珍妮絲!Hi!
Janice is gonna go away now!
她就要走了
I'll be right back.
我馬上回來
Joey! Look who it is!
喬伊,看誰來了
Good. Joey's home.
很好,喬伊回來了
This is so much fun!
這真是太好玩了
This is like a reunion in the hall!
好像是大團圓一樣
Ross,there's someone I want you to say hi to.
羅斯,對,跟某人打個招呼吧
He happened to call.
他恰好打電話來
Hi,Ross. That's right,it's me! How did you know?
羅斯,對,是我.你怎麼會知道?
So,if dogs experience jet lag...
我是說會如果狗也有時差問題
... because of the seven dog years to one human year thing...
因為狗的七年等於人的一年
...when a dog flies from New York to Los Angeles...
那麼狗從紐約飛到洛杉磯
... he doesn't just lose three hours, he loses a week and a half.
損失的不是三小時,而是十天
That's funny!
真好笑
They should be cooking the food soon.
他們應該馬上就做飯了
Oh,good.
oh,好的
Who are they?
她們是誰?
The blond is my ex-wife. The woman touching her is her...
金髮的是我前妻,碰她的是她的
...close,personal friend.
密友
-They're lovers? -lf you want to put a label on it.
-你是指她們是情人? -如果你硬要這麼說的話
-Anything else I should know? -Nope. That's it.
-我還需要知道什麼? -不,就這些了
Oh,and she's pregnant with my baby.
對了,她懷了我的孩子
I always forget that part.
我總是忘了這件事
Hello!
Now we need sage branches and the sacramental wine.
我們需要鼠尾草和沙加緬度酒
All I had is oregano and a Fresca.
我只有牛至葉和佛瑞斯加
That's okay!
那樣也行
Now we need the semen of a righteous man.
現在我們需要正義男子的精液
If we had that,we wouldn't be doing the ritual in the first place.
菲比,如果我們有 現在就無需進行儀式了
-Can we start throwing things in? -Yeah,okay!
-可以丟東西了嗎? -可以了
Okay. Barry's letters.
巴瑞的信
Adam Ritter's boxer shorts.
亞當瑞塔的四角褲
And I have the receipt from my dinner with....
晚餐的收據
-A picture of Scotty Jared naked! -Let me see!
-這是史考帝的裸體照片 -讓我看看!
-He's wearing a sweater. -No.
-他穿著毛衣 -沒有
-Whose MCl card is that? -Mine. Shoot!
-這是誰的MCl卡? -我的.咻!
Remember this number: Nine,seven,four....
趕緊記住號碼:9,7,4….
Okay,and here we have the last of Paolo's grappa.
最後這是保羅的格拉巴酒
Wait,isn't it almost pure
等等,這不是幾乎純…
How can I dump this woman on Valentine's Day?
我怎能在情人節甩掉她
I don't know. You dumped her on New Year's.
天曉得,但你在新年甩掉她
In my next life, I'm coming back as a toilet brush.
下輩子我要當馬桶刷
Hello,funny valentine!
有趣的情人
Hi,just Janice.
珍妮絲
Hello,Joey,our little matchmaker.
喬伊,我們的小媒婆
I could just kiss you all over, and I'm gonna.
我忍不住想吻你
If you don't do it,I will.
如果你不敢,就讓我來開口
-So are you actually from New York? -Not originally. I'm from
-你真的從紐約來的? -本來不是,我從
-You said they'd shoot it without you. -I thought they could.
-你說他們可以自己做 -我以為他們可以
The maxi-pads were a piece of cake. Mini-pads should be that much easier.
最大版都是小菜一碟 最小版當然是更簡單一些了啊
-It's Valentine's Day. -I know,but it's my job.
-但現在是情人節 我知道,但這是我的工作
I'll try to get back as soon as I can.
我會盡量趕回來,抱歉
I'm spending most of my time teaching science...
但我大部分時間都在教科學
...which is funny because that wasn't even my major.
真好笑,我又不是主修科學
Now,that is funny!
真好笑
Do you think it would be too weird if I invited Carol over to join us?
我邀卡蘿過來會很奇怪嗎?
Because she's alone now. And pregnant. And sad.
因為她現在一個人,懷孕了,心情又不好
-I guess. -Are you sure? Carol!
-大概吧 -你確定?卡蘿!
-Wanna join us? -No,I'm fine.
-願意過來坐嗎? -不,我沒事
Come on. These people will scooch down.
來吧,這些人會挪過去的
You guys will scooch,won't you? Let's try scooching! Come on!
你們會挪過去的,對吧? 各位挪過去好嗎,動起來
-Come on. -Thank you.
-拜託 -謝謝
IKristen Riggs,this is Carol Willick. Carol,Kristen.
克莉絲汀,這位是卡蘿 卡蘿,克莉絲汀
-How do you do? -Carol teaches sixth grade.
-你好 -卡蘿教六年級
And Kristen....
克莉絲汀…
IKristen does something...
...that,funnily enough...
最好笑的是
...wasn't even her major!
是她的工作不是她的主修
-Thanks for coming over. -Not at all. It's pretty much our job.
-謝謝你們能來 -沒關係.這是我們的工作
That's why we get the cool hats.
這就是我們為什麼戴這麼酷的帽子啊
-What do we got there? -A piece of sik boxer shorts.
-裡面有什麼東西? 一些真絲四角內褲
Some greeting cards.
問候卡
A half-charred picture of....
燒焦的照片
That guy's hairier than the chief!
這傢伙的體毛比隊長的還濃密
It's a really funny story how this happened.
這件事說來好笑
I was taking out the trash, and Phoebe was burning incense
我拿出垃圾桶,菲比點燃熏香
It's all right.
沒關係.你們不用解釋
This isn't the first boyfriend bonfire we've seen get out of control.
這不是第一件燒燬男友物品失控的事件了
-Third one tonight. -Really?
-這已是今晚的第三件 -真的?
Valentine's is our busiest night of the year.
情人節之夜是我們最忙的時刻
Next time you're burning your ex-boyfriend's stuff:
下一次燒你們前男友的東西時:
One,do it in a well-ventilated area.
第一,在一個通風好的地方
Two,if you wanna burn his clothing, stay away from synthetic fabrics.
第二,如果你們要燒衣服,小心合成纖維的
Three,try to let go of the anger, and learn to love yourself.
第三,試著放掉你們的怒氣 學會愛護自己啊
-I brought you something. -ls it loaded?
-我帶了東西給你 -裝上子彈了沒?
Oh,little candy hearts. "Chan and Jan Forever."
心型糖果「錢德與珍尼絲,永遠」
I had them made special.
我訂做的
Okay,Janice.
ok,珍妮絲…
Hey,Janice.
嗨,珍妮絲…
There's no way to tell you this.
我不該告訴你
At least,there's no new way.
至少沒有別的方法來告訴你
I just don't think things are gonna work out.
我覺得我們不會結果
That's fine.
無所謂
It is?
It is? 是嗎?
Because I know that this isn't the end.
因為我知道我們還沒結束
You see,actually,it is.
事實上已經結束了
No,because you won't let that happen.
不,還沒因為你不會讓它發生的
Don't you know it yet?
難道你還不懂?
You love me,Chandler Bing!
你愛我,錢德.賓
Oh,no,I don't.
不,我不愛
Why do we keep ending up together? New Year's,who invited who?
那麼就捫心自問,我們為何總是會復合? 新年是誰邀誰?
-Valentine's,who asked who into bed? -I did,but
-情人節是誰邀誰上床? -是我,可是…
You seek me out!
我是你尋找的對象
Something deep in your soul calls out to me like a foghorn!
你的內心深處不斷呼喊著我
Janice! Janice!
珍妮絲…珍妮絲…
You push me away, you pull me back!
你推開我,你拉回我!
You want me. You need me.
你要我,你需要我
You can't live without me. And you know it.
你不能沒有我.你知道
You just don't know you know it.
你只是不知道你知道罷了
See?
明白嗎?
Call me!
打電話給我
It's not true. I never called your mother a wolverine.
這不是真的.我沒說你媽是狼人
You did so,I swear to
你有,我發誓
How long has she been in the bathroom?
她上洗手間多久了?
She isn't in the bathroom. Her coat's gone.
我想她不是去上洗手間,她的外套不見了
Well,maybe it's cold in there.
或許是太冷吧
I screwed up my first date in nine years.
或許我搞砸了九年來的第一次約會
-That could be it. -Oh,God.
-有可能 -天哪
You know,this is still pretty hot.
知道嗎,這裡還是很熱
Mushroom.
磨菇
Smile.
微笑
They won't all be like this. Some might stay through dinner.
不會每次都這樣的 還是有些女人會把晚餐吃完的
-I'm sorry. That's not funny. -It's just....
-抱歉,不好笑 -只是
You know the whole "get on with your life" thing?
人們老說要繼續你的人生
Well,do I have to?
我必須嗎?
I'm sitting here with this cute woman...
我和這位美女坐在這兒
...and she's perfectly nice,but that...
她是那麼好
...that's it.
但就這麼吹了
Then I'm here talking to you, and it's easy and it's fun.
我現在又和你聊天,輕鬆又自在
And I don't have to....
我何必…
-I know. -You know?
-我懂 -你懂?
Here's a wacky thought.
我有個瘋狂的念頭
Let's say you and I give it another shot.
我們再試一次好嗎?
I know what you're gonna say. You're a lesbian.
我知道你要說你是個女同志
But what do you say we just put that aside for now.
但何不暫時將它擺在一旁
Let's just stick a pin in it.
完全不去想它
Because we're great together. You can't deny it.
因為我們在一起很開心 這不容你否認
I've got a ring at home that fits you.
我有一個適合你的戒指
I've got lots of pictures with both of us in them.
我有無數我倆一起的照片
And best of all, you're carrying my baby.
最美妙的地方是,你懷著我的孩子
-I mean,how perfect is that? -Ross
-這樣不是很完美嗎? -羅斯
You keep saying that,but there's something right here. I love you.
雖然你一直回絕, 但我仍然想對你說,我愛你
I love you too.
我也愛你
-But -No "but."
-但是 -不要但是
You know that thing we put over here with the pin in it?
你要知道,暫時攔置一旁的事
It's time to take the pin out.
遲早會浮現的
You'll find someone. The right woman is waiting for you.
你會找到對象的,合適的女人正在等著你
It's easy for you to say. You found one already.
你說得倒是輕鬆,你已找到合適的女人
All you need is a woman who likes men, and you'll be set.
你只需找到愛男人的女人即可
Not her.
不是她
So,you guys really slide down a pole?
你們真的從一個柱子上滑下去?
-Absolutely. -That's so cool.
-絕對的 -太酷了
How do you get back up?
那你們怎麼回上面的呢?
Well,we rarely have to return from a fire as quickly.
我們很少需要像著火一樣急的往上去
So,would you guys....
你們這些小伙…
Would you like to,sometime,maybe....
你們願意,有時,可能…
Go for a drink sometime?
有時一起出去喝一杯
Sure,sounds good.
當然,聽起來不錯
We get off at midnight. We'll pick you up then.
我們午夜下班之後,來找你們可以嗎?
Okay. Great!
好啊,太好了
So will you bring the truck?
你們會開消防車過來嗎?
I'll even let you ring the bell.
還會讓你們拉警鈴
-We'll see you later. -Bye! See you later!
再見了…晚安,再見…
Oh,my God!
天啊
See? There you go. The cleansing worked.
看到沒有?清理儀式奏效了
You're right. They're nice guys!
沒錯,他們是好男人
They're firemen guys!
他們是消防隊員
-Tell them you're married? -No. My girlfriend doesn't even know.
-你們有告訴她們你們已婚嗎? -當然沒有,連我女友都不知道